<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ET-LITS</string>
    <string name="add_animal">Add Animal</string>
    <string name="button_save">Save</string>
    <string name="select_date">Select Date...</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome!"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Enter an email</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Enter a password</string>
    <string name="login_alert_title">Sign in error</string>
    <string name="login_unauthorized">The email or password is incorrect.</string>
    <string name="login_server_unreachable">Server is unreachable.</string>
    <string name="login_generic_error">Login failed.</string>
    <string name="sign_out_confirmation_prompt">Do you want to sign out?</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection. Please connect to wi-fi or mobile data.</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection_short">No internet</string>
    <!--Sync-->
    <string name="sync_init_dialog_title">Data Initialization</string>
    <string name="sync_init_dialog_msg">To get started, the app needs to download the necessary data.</string>
    <string name="sync_init_dialog_msg_resume">Data initialization has not finished. The app needs to complete data download.</string>
    <string name="sync_start_data_download">START DATA DOWNLOAD</string>
    <string name="sync_resume_data_download">RESUME DATA DOWNLOAD</string>
    <string name="sync_view_last_attempt">VIEW LAST ATTEMPT</string>
    <string name="sync_exit_app">EXIT APP</string>
    <string name="title_data_sync">Data Sync</string>
    <string name="btn_sync_start">START</string>
    <string name="btn_sync_stop">STOP</string>
    <string name="sync_date">%1$s</string>
    <string name="sync_stopped_msg">%1$s</string>
    <string name="synced_by">Synced by: %1$s</string>
    <string name="sync_init_dialog_exit_no">NO</string>
    <string name="sync_init_dialog_exit_yes">YES, STOP &amp; EXIT THE APP</string>
    <string name="sync_init_dialog_exit_msg">Initial data download is in progress. Do you want to stop and exit the app?</string>
    <string name="sync_info_text">During data synchronization, the mobile app downloads from the ET-LITS web application the data to be stored locally for repeated and offline use. Changes done on the mobile app are sent back to the ET-LITS web application for final validation and permanent storage. Until then, locally stored data is not officially recognized. Some data can be changed via the ET-LITS website. If this data is not refreshed on your device, then your changes that rely on it may be rejected during data sync. Locally stored changes may also get lost due to device damage or unexpected data storage issues. Data synchronization must be done as often as possible, immediately the internet connection is available.</string>
    <string name="sync_records">records</string>
    <string name="sync_history_icon_txt">History</string>
    <string name="sync_view_details">View Details</string>
    <string name="sync_update_details">Update Details</string>
    <string name="sync_records_sent">Records sent: %1$s</string>
    <string name="sync_records_not_sent">Records not sent: %1$s</string>
    <string name="sync_records_received">Records received: %1$s</string>
    <string name="sync_errors">Errors</string>
    <string name="sync_error_server_unreachable">ET-LITS server cannot be reached.</string>
    <string name="sync_error_401">Authentication error occured.</string>
    <string name="sync_error_generic">Sync failed. Unknown sync error.</string>
    <string name="sync_status_not_started">Not Started</string>
    <string name="sync_status_initializing">Initializing</string>
    <string name="sync_status_in_progress">In Progress</string>
    <string name="sync_status_completed">Success</string>
    <string name="sync_status_stopping">Stopping</string>
    <string name="sync_status_stopped">Stopped</string>
    <string name="sync_status_partial">Partial</string>
    <string name="sync_status_failed">Failed</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="menu_sync">Sync</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_animals">Animal</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_logout">Sign out</string>
    <string name="menu_move">Move</string>
    <string name="sync_stopped_by_user">Stopped by user</string>
    <string name="sync_status">Sync Status</string>
    <string name="sync_data_may_be_stale">Data may be stale</string>
    <string name="sync_info_close">Close</string>
    <string name="home_establishment_search">Establishment Search</string>
    <string name="establishment_title">Establishment</string>
    <string name="establishment_summary_pic">PIC</string>
    <string name="establishment_type">Type</string>
    <string name="establishment_phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="establishment_not_specified">not specified</string>
    <string name="establishment_mobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="establishment_alternative_postal_address">Alternative Postal Address</string>
    <string name="establishment_physical_address">Physical Address</string>
    <string name="establishment_latitude_longitude">Latitude/Longitude</string>
    <string name="establishment_name">Name</string>
    <string name="establishment_email">Email</string>
    <string name="establishment_use_by_default">Use By Default</string>
    <string name="selected_establishment">Selected Establishment</string>
    <string name="establishment_set_default_msg">Default establishment has been set to: %1$s</string>
    <string name="establishment_search_hint">EID Lookup</string>
    <string name="home_stakeholders">Stakeholders</string>
    <string name="home_documents">Documents</string>
    <string name="animal_trace">Trace</string>
    <string name="animals_trace">Trace</string>
    <string name="animals_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="animals_health">Health</string>
    <string name="animals_register_tag">Register/Tag</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_on_holding_ground">On Holding Ground</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_establishment_eid">Establishment EID*</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_lookup_eid">Lookup EID</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_date_move_off">Date Move-Off*</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_select_date">Select Date ...</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_establishment">Establishment</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_date_move_on">Date Move-On*</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_date_identification">Date Identification*</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_animals_identified_and_registered">Animals identified and registered</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_herd_specie">Herd Specie*</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_add_animal">Add Animal</string>
    <string name="reg_enter_animal_id">Animal ID</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_animal_id">Animal ID*</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_add_next_animal">Add Next Animal</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_done">Done</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_breed">Breed*</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_select">Select...</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_sex">Sex*</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_age">Age (Months)</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_age_hint">Age in months...</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_dead">Dead</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_seller">Seller</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_seller_hint">Seller</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_field_required">Required</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_animal_id_required">Animal Id field is required</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_sex_required">Sex field is required</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_breed_required">Breed field is required</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_age_required">Age field is required</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_animal_id_invalid">Invalid animal Id. Allowed format is: ET 0000000001</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_age_invalid">Invalid Age. Allowed range is 1 to 300 months.</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_age_months">%1$s months</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_animal_detail_title">Animal Details</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_title">Animal Registrations</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_date_required">Date required</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_eid_required">Establishment ID required</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_date_in_future">Selected date should not be in future.</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_identification_date_after_move_off">Date Move-Off must be after or same as Date Identification</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_move_off_date_after_move_on">Date Move-On must be on or after Date Move-Off.</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_treatments_applied">Treatments Applied</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_finish_registration">Finish Registration</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_view_registrations">View Registrations</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_no_animals_registered">No Animals Registered</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_animal_list_empty_error">At least one animal must be registered.</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_dialog_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="card_animals">Animals</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_animal_list_info">"Please tap on ‘Add Animal' to enter a new animal in the list or edit icon to change the animal details.\nTap on the 'Next' button or swipe left to continue your activities. "</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_move_events_info">You are in process to register animals on the holding ground.\nFor each animal an Move-Off from holding ground and a Move-On to establishment will be created.\nPlease enter the EID of the holding ground and the dates of tagging and movements.\nEID = Establishment ID\nFields marked with * are mandatory\nTap on the \'Next\' button or swipe left to continue your activities.</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_treatments_info">If the animals were treated with treatments at arrival on the establishment you can indicate the kind of treatment by tapping the respective checkbox.\nPlease note that the treatments indicated will be registered for each animal in the list of animals.\nTap on the \'Finish Registration\' button to complete the animals’ registration.</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_animal_detail_info">Tap on the \'Dead\' animal toggle if the animal was found dead during transport.\nTap on the \'Done\' button to complete current animal data entry and return to the animal registration form.\nTap on the \'Add Next Animal\' to complete the current animal data entry and open new Animal Details to continue registering the next animal.</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_leave_the_form">Leave the form?</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_leave_form_msg">Any changes entered will be lost. Are you sure you want to leave?</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_leave_form_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_leave_form_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_close_snackbar_msg">%1$s animals registered</string>
    <string name="animal_reg_close_snackbar_action">SYNC</string>

    <!--Terms of Use - Placeholder content-->
    <string name="ToU">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="ToU_welcome_txt">Welcome to our site. We maintain this web site as a service to our members. By using our site, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms of use. Please review the following terms carefully. If you do not agree to these terms, you should not use this site.</string>
    <string name="ToU_AoA_title">1. Acceptance of Agreement.</string>
    <string name="ToU_AoA_txt">You agree to the terms and conditions outlined in this Terms of Use Agreement ("Agreement") with respect to our site (the "Site"). This Agreement constitutes the entire and only agreement between us and you, and supersedes all prior or contemporaneous agreements, representations, warranties and understandings with respect to the Site, the content, products or services provided by or through the Site, and the subject matter of this Agreement. This Agreement may be amended at any time by us from time to time without specific notice to you. The latest Agreement will be posted on the Site, and you should review this Agreement prior to using the Site.</string>
    <string name="ToU_copyright_title">2. Copyright.</string>
    <string name="ToU_copyright_txt">The content, organization, graphics, design, compilation, magnetic translation, digital conversion and other matters related to the Site are protected under applicable copyrights, trademarks and other proprietary (including but not limited to intellectual property) rights. The copying, redistribution, use or publication by you of any such matters or any part of the Site, except as allowed by Section 4, is strictly prohibited. You do not acquire ownership rights to any content, document or other materials viewed through the Site. The posting of information or materials on the Site does not constitute a waiver of any right in such information and materials.</string>
    <string name="ToU_SM_title">3. Service Marks.</string>
    <string name="ToU_SM_txt">Products and names mentioned on the Site may be trademarks of their respective owners.</string>
    <string name="ToU_LRU_title">4. Limited Rights to Use.</string>
    <string name="ToU_LRU_txt">The viewing, printing or downloading of any content, graphic, form or document from the Site grants you only a limited, nonexclusive license for use solely by you for your own personal use and not for republication, distribution, assignment, sublicense, sale, preparation of derivative works or other use. No part of any content, form or document may be reproduced in any form or incorporated into any information retrieval system, electronic or mechanical, other than for your personal use (but not for resale or redistribution).</string>
    <string name="ToU_EDM_title">5. Editing, Deleting, Modification</string>
    <string name="ToU_EDM_txt">We reserve the right in our sole discretion to edit or delete any documents, information or other content appearing on the Site.</string>
    <string name="ToU_Indem_title">6. Indemnification.</string>
    <string name="ToU_Indem_txt">You agree to indemnify, defend and hold us and our partners, attorneys, staff, advertisers, product and service providers, and affiliates (collectively, "Affiliated Parties") harmless from any liability, loss, claim and expense, including reasonable attorney\'s fees, related to your violation of this Agreement or use of the Site.</string>
    <string name="ToU_Nontransferable_title">7. Nontransferable.</string>
    <string name="ToU_Nontransferable_txt">Your right to use the Site is not transferable. Any password or right given to you to obtain information or documents is not transferable.</string>
    <string name="ToU_DaL_title">8. Disclaimer and Limits.</string>
    <string name="ToU_DaL_txt">THE INFORMATION FROM OR THROUGH THE SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS-IS," "AS AVAILABLE," AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ARE DISCLAIMED (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE DISCLAIMER OF ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE). THE INFORMATION AND SERVICES MAY CONTAIN BUGS, ERRORS, PROBLEMS OR OTHER LIMITATIONS. WE AND OUR AFFILIATED PARTIES HAVE NO LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR YOUR USE OF ANY INFORMATION OR SERVICE. IN PARTICULAR, BUT NOT AS A LIMITATION THEREOF, WE AND OUR AFFILIATED PARTIES ARE NOT LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS, LOSS OF PROFITS, LITIGATION, OR THE LIKE), WHETHER BASED ON BREACH OF CONTRACT, BREACH OF WARRANTY, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), PRODUCT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THE NEGATION OF DAMAGES SET FORTH ABOVE ARE FUNDAMENTAL ELEMENTS OF THE BASIS OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN US AND YOU. THIS SITE AND THE PRODUCTS, SERVICES, AND INFORMATION PRESENTED WOULD NOT BE PROVIDED WITHOUT SUCH LIMITATIONS. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM US THROUGH THE SITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY, REPRESENTATION OR GUARANTEE NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THIS AGREEMENT. WE DO NOT PROVIDE LEGAL ADVICE NOR ENTER INTO ANY ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP.\nALL RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY DAMAGES CAUSED BY VIRUSES CONTAINED WITHIN THE ELECTRONIC FILE CONTAINING THE FORM OR DOCUMENT IS DISCLAIMED. WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND THAT MAY RESULT FROM USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE OUR SITE. OUR MAXIMUM LIABILITY TO YOU UNDER ALL CIRCUMSTANCES WILL BE EQUAL TO THE PURCHASE PRICE YOU PAY FOR ANY GOODS, SERVICES OR INFORMATION.</string>
    <string name="ToU_UoI_title">9. Use of Information.</string>
    <string name="ToU_UoI_txt">We reserve the right, and you authorize us, to the use and assignment of all information regarding Site uses by you and all information provided by you in any manner consistent with our Privacy Policy. All remarks, suggestions, ideas, graphics, or other information communicated by you to us through the Site (collectively, the "Submission") will forever be the property of Liferay. Liferay will not be required to treat any Submission as confidential, and will not be liable for any ideas for its business (including without limitation, product, service or advertising ideas) and will not incur any liability as a result of any similarities that may appear in future Liferay products, services or operations. Without limitation, Liferay will have exclusive ownership of all present and future existing rights to the Submission of every kind and nature everywhere. Liferay will be entitled to use the Submission for any commercial or other purpose whatsoever, without compensation to you or any other person sending the Submission. You acknowledge that you are responsible for whatever material you submit, and you, not Liferay, have full responsibility for the message, including its legality, reliability, appropriateness, originality, and copyright.</string>
    <string name="ToU_TPS_title">10. Third-Party Services.</string>
    <string name="ToU_TPS_txt">We may allow access to or advertise third-party product or service providers ("Merchants") from which you may purchase certain goods or services. You understand that we do not operate or control the products or services offered by Merchants. Merchants are responsible for all aspects of order processing, fulfillment, billing and customer service. We are not a party to the transactions entered into between you and Merchants. You agree that use of such Merchants is AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND IS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND BY US, EXPRESSED, IMPLIED OR OTHERWISE INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF TITLE, FITNESS FOR PURPOSE, MERCHANTABILITY OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES ARE WE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES ARISING FROM THE TRANSACTIONS BETWEEN YOU AND MERCHANTS OR FOR ANY INFORMATION APPEARING ON MERCHANT SITES OR ANY OTHER SITE LINKED TO OUR SITE.</string>
    <string name="ToU_TPMP_title">11. Third-Party Merchant Policies.</string>
    <string name="ToU_TPMP_txt">All rules, policies (including privacy policies) and operating procedures of Merchants will apply to you while on such sites. We are not responsible for information provided by you to Merchants. We and the Merchants are independent contractors and neither party has authority to make any representations or commitments on behalf of the other.</string>
    <string name="ToU_PP_title">12. Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="ToU_PP_txt">Our Privacy Policy, as it may change from time to time, is a part of this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="ToU_payments_title">13. Payments.</string>
    <string name="ToU_payments_txt">You represent and warrant that if you are purchasing something from us or from Merchants that (i) any credit information you supply is true and complete, (ii) charges incurred by you will be honored by your credit card company, and (iii) you will pay the charges incurred by you at the posted prices, including any applicable taxes.</string>
    <string name="ToU_SL_title">14. Securities Laws.</string>
    <string name="ToU_SL_txt">This Site may include statements concerning our operations, prospects, strategies, financial condition, future economic performance and demand for our products or services, as well as our intentions, plans and objectives (particularly with respect to product and service offerings), that are forward-looking statements. These statements are based upon a number of assumptions and estimates which are subject to significant uncertainties, many of which are beyond our control. When used on our Site, words like "anticipates," "expects," "believes," "estimates," "seeks," "plans," "intends," "will" and similar expressions are intended to identify forward-looking statements designed to fall within securities law safe harbors for forward-looking statements. The Site and the information contained herein does not constitute an offer or a solicitation of an offer for sale of any securities. None of the information contained herein is intended to be, and shall not be deemed to be, incorporated into any of our securities-related filings or documents.</string>
    <string name="ToU_LOWS_title">15. Links to Other Web Sites.</string>
    <string name="ToU_LOWS_txt">The Site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy or opinions express in such web sites, and such web sites are not investigated, monitored or checked for accuracy or completeness by us. Inclusion of any linked web site on our Site does not imply approval or endorsement of the linked web site by us. If you decide to leave our Site and access these third-party sites, you do so at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="ToU_CCA_title">16. Copyrights and Copyright Agents.</string>
    <string name="ToU_CCA_txt">We respect the intellectual property of others, and we ask you to do the same. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide our Copyright Agent the following information:\n\n(a) An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;\n\n(b) A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;\n\n(c) A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Site;\n\n(d) Your address, telephone number, and email address;\n\n(e) A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and\n\n(f) A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your Notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner\'s behalf. Our Copyright Agent for Notice of claims of copyright infringement on the Site can be reached by directing an e-mail to the Copyright Agent at admin@liferay.com</string>
    <string name="ToU_PPSO_title">17. Proposed Product and Service Offerings.</string>
    <string name="ToU_PPSO_txt">All descriptions of proposed products and services are based on assumptions subject to change and you should not rely on the availability or functionality of products or services until they are actually offered through the Site. We reserve the right in its sole discretion to determine how registration and other promotions will be awarded. This determination includes, without limitation, the scope, nature and timing of all such awards.</string>
    <string name="ToU_IPR_title">18. Information and Press Releases.</string>
    <string name="ToU_IPR_txt">The Site contains information and press releases about us. While this information was believed to be accurate as of the date prepared, we disclaim any duty or obligation to update this information or any press releases. Information about companies other than ours contained in the press release or otherwise, should not be relied upon as being provided or endorsed by us.</string>
    <string name="ToU_miscellaneous_title">19. Miscellaneous.</string>
    <string name="ToU_miscellaneous_txt">This Agreement shall be treated as though it were executed and performed in Los Angeles, CA, and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California (without regard to conflict of law principles). Any cause of action by you with respect to the Site (and/or any information, products or services related thereto) must be instituted within one (1) year after the cause of action arose or be forever waived and barred. All actions shall be subject to the limitations set forth in Section 8 and Section 10. The language in this Agreement shall be interpreted as to its fair meaning and not strictly for or against either party. All legal proceedings arising out of or in connection with this Agreement shall be brought solely in Los Angeles, CA. You expressly submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of said courts and consents to extra-territorial service of process. Should any part of this Agreement be held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed consistent with applicable law and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect. To the extent that anything in or associated with the Site is in conflict or inconsistent with this Agreement, this Agreement shall take precedence. Our failure to enforce any provision of this Agreement shall not be deemed a waiver of such provision nor of the right to enforce such provision.</string>
    <string name="ToU_disagree_btn_txt">I DISAGREE</string>
    <string name="ToU_agree_btn_txt">I AGREE</string>

    <!--    About ET-LITS - placeholder content-->
    <string name="about_et_lits">About ET-LITS</string>
    <string name="et_lits_desc">Ethiopian Livestock Identification and Traceability System (ET-LITS) is a mobile app designed to assist in animal identification, recording and movement processes on the field. The system is owned and managed by the Government of Ethiopia.</string>
    <string name="et_lits_features">Features\n\n\t<li>Secured access and data exchange</li>\n\t<li>Offline data entry</li>\n\t<li>Customized forms</li>\n\t<li>Data validation</li>\n\t<li>GPS location tracking</li>\n\t<li>Image and file attachments</li>\n\t<li>Data syncing with ET-LITS web application</li></string>

    <string name="device_model">Current device model: %1$s</string>
    <string name="android_virsion">Current Android version: %1$s</string>
    <string name="build_virsion">Build version: %1$s</string>
    <string name="build_date">Build date: %1$s</string>
</resources>